

# Rafał Bierzanek

# software tester/ fronted developer

# **My Contact**

🕍 rafbierzanek@gmail.com



+48 501782755



Warsaw



www.linkedin.com/in/rafał-bierzanek



github.com/RafalBie

https://rafalbie.github.io/portfolio/

#### **Hard Skill**

Knowledge of ISTQB FL Create scenarios and test cases Basic knowledge HTML/CSS/JAVA SCRIPT/REACT **UX DESIGN WORDPRESS** Development tools: VS Code Version control system: GIT Jira

Postman API MS Office

#### **Soft Skill**

Effective communication ability Developed analytical thinking skills Cooperation **Emotional Intelligence** Multitasking Trainable Critical thinking

#### **Additional Education**

Training "ISTQB Foundation Level" testerzy .pl 10.2022

Training "Profession Tester" testerzy .pl 11.2021

**UX Designer | Future Collars** 02.2020

Fronted Developer | Future Collars

Wordpress with SEO positioning | GO WORK

### **Education**

#### **About Me**

I have been working in the real estate industry for the last few years, working in all specializations: property management, real estate appraisal and sales brokerage. I made the decision to rearrange 4 years ago and during this period I have had many trainings, webinars, online courses and participated in projects related to training in the IT industries. Analyzing my hard knowledge in the field of IT and knowing my interpersonal communication and analytical skills confirmed in the real estate industry, I'm sure I made the right decision, and I am very eager to expand my knowledge through training and mentoring in testing and coding.

### **Professional Experience**

TDS SOFT | Software tester

08.2022 - Present

Create scenarios and test cases Manual testing of a web application Reporting bugs using Jira Working in an agile team

Freelancing | Web development by Wordpress

2018 - 2019

CEO | Home Factor

2014 - present

real estate broker, short-term rental management

With Money | Real estate appraiser

2013 - 2014

Krupa Nieruchomości | Real estate broker

# **Project Experience**

testerzy.pl | practice "manual testing" Create scenarios and test cases 12.2021

Future Collars | final training project with UX Design "Redesign procesu dodawania ogłoszenia w portalu Morizon.pl"

Future Collars | Final training project with Fronted Developer "weather application" 12.2019

## Languages

English - B2

Spanish - A2

Russian - Al